Guide to the Dept. of Government honors theses, 1991-2018
Dept. of Government honors theses, 1991-2018
- "Help a Sister Out - How Women in Congress are Supporting Female Candidates Through Leadership PACs and Member Donations", 2016; Fraling, Michelle (Box 6)
- "The Search for Liberalism in Kosovo", 2016; Furman, Jonathan (Box 6)
- "Pork and Polarization: How the Earmark Moratorium Exacerbates Partisan Polarization In the U.S. House of Representatives", 2016; Jacobson, Nathan (Box 6)
- "Reality Check - Understanding the Effects of Exposing Partisan Americans to Unanticipated Information About Their Political Leaders", 2016; Leff, Benjamin (Box 6)
- "Police Organizations and Racial Rhetoric: The Link Between Social Unrest and Racialized Political Rhetoric From the Police", 2016; Lewis, Alexander (Box 6)
- "Rsidential Segregation and Its Impact on Voter Turnout - A Neighborhood-Level Analysis of Political Participation", 2016; Raskin, Nicholas (Box 6)
- "Explaining Extreme Right Voting in Denmark and Sweden: Looking at Contextual Factors", 2016; Stokes, Margo (Box 6)
- "Shifting Into Neutral: Explaining State Neutrality in Immigration Policy in the United States", 2016; Sussman, Caitlan (Box 6)
- "Imperium Legum Non Hominum: A Constitutional Theory of Democratic Peace", 2016; Toomey, James (Box 6)
- "Online Anonymity: A Political Right or a Haven for Criminality", 2016; Velkes, Gabrielle (Box 6)
- "Is The Roberts Courting Business: Class Action in the Wake of Walmart Stores, Inc. v. Dukes", 2016; Wilhelm, Samantha (Box 6)
- "Gender Quotas: Power in the Numbers", 2017; Clark, Lauren (Box 6)
- "Business Improvement Districts in DC: An Exploration of BID Impact on Urban Governance", 2017; Crawford, Caroline (Box 6)
- "Understanding Religion and State Formation: A Comparative Analysis of Saudi Arabia and Indonesia", 2017; DiGiacomo, Christian (Box 6)
- "America's Photographic Memory: Iconic War Photograpy and Collective Understanding", 2017; Klinek, Savanna (Box 6)
- "Violence in Latin America: The Cuban Exception", 2017; LeCaire, Troy (Box 6)
- "Still Linked? Afro-Caribbean Immigrants and the Politics of Incorporation", 2017; Williams-Libert, Kennedi (Box 6)
- "Who Cares: How Racial and Economoic Context Affect Public Support for Welfare Spending", 2018; Biggs, Rubin Danberg (Box 7)
- "The New "Welfare": Social Security Disabiility Insurance, Supplemental Security Income, and American Conservatism"", 2018; Cho, Christopher (Box 7)
- "The Effectiveness of European Union Development Cooperation Policy in the Maghreb: An Analysis of the European Neighborhood Policy", 2018; Bray, Marissa (Box 7)
- "Competitive Effects of Private School Voucher Programs on Teacher Turnover in Wisconsin Public Schools", 2018; Gartland, Jeremy (Box 7)
- "How We Got to Kelo: The Rise of Eminent Domain Opposition Prior to 2005", 2018; Glanzel, Michael (Box 7)
- "Chile: An Enigma of Neoliberalism, Inequality, and Social Development", 2018; Gullo, Anthony (Box 7)
- "The Lost Republikflucht: Exit as a Social Phenomenon", 2018; Hwang, Sohyeon (Box 7)
- "The Effect of Gerrymandering on Voter Turnout in American Congressional Elections", 2018; Kanengiser, Henry (Box 7)
- "Perspectives on Treatment Courts: A Case Study", 2018; Kirshner, Elie (Box 7)
- "Fatah vs. Hamas: Assessing the Feasibility of Reconciliation in 2018", Kramer, Abigail (Box 7)
- "Disney's Jewish Shtick", 2018; Lyass, Alexandra (Box 7)
- "A Feminist Analysis of IX Enforcement Against Campus Sexual Violence", 2018; Markowitz, Caroline (Box 7)
- "The Crisis for Campus Conservatives: How Presidential Candidate Donald J. Trump Divided College Republicans in 2016", 2018; McLaughlin, Austin (Box 7)
- "The Politics of Central Banking: How Financial and Partisan Biases Shape Monetary Policy at the Federal Reserve", 2018; Monaghan, Paul (Box 7)
- "The Reinvention of an Age-Old Truth: An Analysis of Discriminatory State Policies After Shelby County vs. Holder", 2018; Palmiter, Morgan (Box 7)
- "Analysis of Causal Factors Motivating Global Changes to Levels of Suspicion Required for Warrantless Searches and the Resulting Policy Convergence from 2000 to 2010", 2018; Pecaro, Jacqueline (Box 7)
- "Female Legislators and State Environment: Understanding the Lack of Female Representatives in State Legislatures Through the Influence of Wage Inequality", 2018; Saber, Rebecca (Box 7)
- "Convergence or Divergence? A Comparative Analysis of China's Counter-Terrorism Cooperation with the United States and Russia", 2018; Shen, Sun (Box 7)
- "Unfulfilled Promise Zones: How Policy Implementation Impacts Voter Awareness and Accountability Behavior", 2018; Sierks, Cara (Box 7)
- "Political Memes and Affective Polarization in America", 2018; Tan, Catherina (Box 7)
- "Lessons from the Khmer Rouge: The Legacies of Colonization", 2018; Teo, Ming Hui Magdalene (Box 7)